Alyssa D. Crechiolo

alyssa.webdev@gmail.com | 810-522-7077 | LinkedIn | GitHub | Detroit, MI

SUMMARY

Compliance auditor turned ambitious bootcamp front end developer. After years of working for a high-volume law firm, I decided that it was time to start chasing my dream of working in tech, so I enrolled in Grand Circus' front end bootcamp. During this 10 week program, I realized that thinking logically and creatively while collaborating with others to create intuitive, cutting-edge user experiences was incredibly fulfilling and never once felt like work. This enthusiastic, quirky, creative, and team-oriented problem solver is now more confident than ever that this is the right field for me and I am beyond excited to finally join the tech industry and continue expanding my technical skill set.

EDUCATION

Grand Circus Front End Bootcamp Detroit, MI

June 2020

Projects:

- El Gato Galaxy, Group Project Memory Game HTML, CSS, & JavaScript
- Pirate Bae, Group Project Movie Database Angular, HTML, TypeScript, & CSS;
- <u>Tents 'N' Trails</u>, Final Group Project Angular, HTML, TypeScript, & CSS.

Grand Valley State University, Allendale, MI Bachelors of Science, Sociology

January 2016

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript

- Angular
- SQL
- Node.js
- Web APIs

- UI Design
- TDD
- Express.js
- Git/GitHub

TECHNICAL SKILLS (IN PROCESS)

SASS

React

Wordpress

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Compliance Auditor

August 2017 - June 2020

Stenger & Stenger, PC, Grand Rapids, MI (remote)

- Assisted and supported Director of Compliance with internal control procedures.
- Monitored 20 30 calls daily and promptly provided feedback to the collections team.
- Completed 9 monthly client audits prior to the deadline date and assisted on 3 others.
- Reviewed and resolved complaints within less than a 24 hour turnaround time.

Team Lead, Processor, E-Commerce Technician Goodwill of Greater Grand Rapids, Grand Rapids, MI June 2012 - June 2017

- Consistently exceed production goals by 40% or more.
- Requested cross-training in 3 other roles to increase my value to the company and my team.
- Improved customer retention through daily engagement with regular and new customers.
- Received praise from the VP of Operations for providing exceptional customer service. .

Document Management Coordinator Great Lakes Medical Supply, Warren, MI March 2009 - July 2011

- Diligently maintained over 100 customer accounts to ensure orders were shipped in a timely manner.
- Significantly decreased the amount of incomplete prescriptions received from physicians.
- Constructed guidelines that were distributed office-wide to help reduce easy to miss errors.
- Became the go-to person for problematic accounts and physicians' offices.
- Performed medical data entry with the utmost precision.